thundertix.com 2017-06-06

# ThunderTix | Privacy Policy - ThunderTix commitment to protecting your information

Updated November 3, 2011

ThunderTix is committed to protecting your personal information, and we respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how we use and protect the personal information we collect when you attempt to or actual do order a ticket using our Website or Website Services. This Policy applies to all users of ThunderTix.com (the “Website”) and the ThunderTix services (the “Website Services”) along with and subject to the [Terms of Use available here](http://www.thundertix.com/terms-of-use/) and incorporated herein by reference.

By using the Website, you are accepting the terms of this policy and agree that they are adequate and sufficient to protect your privacy.

**Collecting Your Personal Information**

As an eCommerce website, ThunderTix may collect personal information from you such as your name, phone number, and email address, on behalf of our clients (the “Venues”). When you buy or attempt to buy a ticket from a Venue using the Website and the Website Services, ThunderTix collects additional information on behalf of the Venues, including, without limitation, financial information from you (credit card data, billing address, etc.).

You also provide non-personal information about your computer and about your activities on the Website. This information includes your IP address, your browser type, the date and time you access the site, and the website that referred you to our site.

**Data Protection**

ThunderTix has security measures in place to help safeguard your information from unauthorized access or disclosure. Only ThunderTix employees or active Venue employees, are permitted to access your personal information. We also encrypt all credit card data before it is sent from your computer through the Internet Gateway. ThunderTix does not store any credit card data except for last 4 digits of the card, and this is available only so that the Venue can ensure the buyer’s identity in the case that a ticket is lost or misplaced.

We take precautions to ensure the security of your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee that hackers or unauthorized personnel will not gain access to your personal information despite our efforts. In using the Website, your information will travel through third party infrastructures which are not under our control.

**Our Use of Your Information**

ThunderTix may use information that we collect about you in one or more of the following ways, among others:

  * Processing the payment for tickets you purchase
  * Delivering tickets, products and services made on the Website
  * To include you in Venue mailing lists in which you choose to participate;
  * To communicate with you by e-mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about events and tickets you purchase;
  * To enforce our terms and conditions;
  * To better protect you from or identify fraudulent transactions;

**Other Websites**

Third parties have their own privacy policies that govern their use of your information. There are a number of places on the Website where you may click on a link to access other websites that don’t operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on a link on the Website from an event to the performer’s own website, you may be taken to a website that we don’t control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you. Importantly, these third parties will have their own privacy policies describing how they use and disclose your personal information. Those policies will govern the use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once you or we have shared it with those third parties. If you want to learn more about other entities’ privacy practices, please review the websites of those third parties. Privacy policies are typically located at the bottom of the web page you are visiting.

At no time does ThunderTix use your personal information to send commercial or promotional emails. In the case that a commercial or promotional email is sent to you from the Venue where you purchased tickets, you should consult with the Venue to opt out of receiving such messages.

**Children’s Privacy**

The Website is not intended for children under 13, and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. Children aged 13 or older should not submit any personal information without the permission of their parents or guardians. By using the Website, you are representing that you are at least 18, or that you are at least 13 years old and have your parents’ permission to use the Website.

**Visiting Our Website from Outside the United States**

This Privacy Policy covers the collection of information on the Website from U.S. and Canadian residents. If you are visiting the Website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated.

U.S. data protection and other laws may not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we take steps to ensure that your privacy is protected.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “Updated at” date at the top of this page. If we make any changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by displaying a notice of the changes on our website. We recommend that you check the Website periodically to be aware of any changes in our privacy or other policies.
